oxygenofficepro.com 2019-06-09

# OxygenOfficePro.Com > > > 100% Free MS Compatable Office Suite

OxygenOfficePro.Com is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we have prepared this privacy statement to disclose and describe our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

**Notice and Disclosure**

In general, you may visit this website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. OxygenOfficePro.Com collects domain information from your visit to customize and improve your experience on our website. Some portions of this website may require you to give us personally identifiable information, which is information that enables us to identify you, such as your name, email or other address. If you opt to provide us that sort of information, we also may use it for purposes such as verifying your identity, sending you information or contacting you. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

It is our intent to inform you before we collect personally identifiable information. You will have the option of not providing the information, in which case you may still be able to access other portions of this website, although you may not be able to access certain programs or services.

**Data Security Quality and Access**

OxygenOfficePro.Com intent is to strictly protect the security of your personal information; honor your choice for its intended use; and carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.OxygenOfficePro.Com strives to keep your information and data accurate, complete and current. We will promptly take steps to correct any inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information which we are made aware of.

**Business Relationships**

This website contains links to other websites. OxygenOfficePro.Com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Cookies**

Portions of this website use cookies to keep track of your visit, or to deliver content specific to your interests. A "Cookie" is a small amount of data transferred to your browser and read by the Web server that placed it there. It works as a sort of identification card, recording your preferences and previously entered information. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to accept or reject it.
